<?xml version="1.0"?>
<body>
    <menu>
        <changelog>
            <meta>
                <title>Changelog</title>
                <version_prefix>Version</version_prefix>
            </meta>
            <version verNum=".01"><![CDATA[
           Start
        ]]></version>
        </changelog>
        <save>
            <meta>
                <title>Saving</title>
            </meta>
            <manual_save>Save Manually</manual_save>
            <export_list>Export Current List</export_list>
            <import_list>Import List to Current</import_list>
            <list_label>Export/Import List</list_label>
            <list_comment>Export's the current list in a plain-text format you can paste and share with others</list_comment>
            <input_label>Export/Import Savefile</input_label>
            <export_button>Export</export_button>
            <export_comment><![CDATA[Click Export to export to your clipboard (ctrl-v somewhere else).<br>
              Paste a save and click Import to import.]]></export_comment>
            <import_button>Import</import_button>
            <import_comment><![CDATA[
              WARNING: Import will break the game if invalid save. Empty import will hard clear the game<br>
              If you reaaallly want to edit your save file, ]]></import_comment>
            <import_hover_special>hover me</import_hover_special>
            <import_hover_special_tooltip>
                <![CDATA[In the console, use decode("pasted savefile"), edit, then encode('pasted savefile'), then import it<br>This is mainly for fixing broken savefiles - don't be a cheater.]]></import_hover_special_tooltip>
        </save>
        <faq>
            <meta>
                <title>FAQ</title>
                <q_prefix><![CDATA[<b>Q:</b>]]></q_prefix>
                <a_prefix><![CDATA[<b>A:</b>]]></a_prefix>
            </meta>
            <q_a>
                <q>What do stats do?</q>
                <a>Hover over "Stats" for how they work. What stats are important depend on what actions you need that
                    uses them.
                </a>
            </q_a>
            <q_a>
                <q>Short runs seem better.</q>
                <a>Short runs are better, for the early game and current balance. But as your runs get longer and you accrue
                    talent and soulstones, longer runs become more useful.
                </a>
            </q_a>
            <q_a>
                <q>What should my first goal be?</q>
                <a>Finish the Crystal quest for mana, then do any other ones.
                </a>
            </q_a>
        </faq>
        <options>
            <meta>
                <title>Options</title>
            </meta>
            <localization_title>Language</localization_title>
            <theme_title>Theme</theme_title>
            <theme>
                <normal>Normal</normal>
            </theme>
            <theme>
                <dark>Dark</dark>
            </theme>
            <theme>
                <cubic>Cubic</cubic>
            </theme>
            <!--changed discord link for analytical reasons-->
            <discord>
                <link>https://discord.gg/dnKA6Xd</link>
                <title>Discord Link</title>
            </discord>
            <adblock_warning>WARNING: For some reason, Adblock Plus can cause massive lag. This game won't ever have ads, so if your game is freezing frequently, please disable it on this page.
            </adblock_warning>
            <pause_audio_cue>Ping on pause</pause_audio_cue>
            <hotkeys>Hotkeys</hotkeys>
            <hotkeys_tooltip><![CDATA[
                Spacebar: Pause/play<br>
                R: Restart<br>
                B: Toggle bonus seconds<br>
                1-5: Select loadout 1-5<br>
                Shift+1-5: Select and load loadout 1-5<br>
                +/-: Increase/decrease action list size<br>
                Shift+S: Save current list to selected loudout<br>
                Shift+L: Load selected loudout<br>
                Shift+C: Clear current list<br>
                Right/D: Show next zone<br>
                Left/A: Show previous zone<br>
                Shift+Right/D: Show action stories<br>
                Shift+Left/A: Show action options<br>
                Shift+Z: Undo most recent change to action list
        ]]></hotkeys_tooltip>
            <update_rate>Updates per second:</update_rate>
        </options>
    </menu>
    <tutorial><![CDATA[
      TUTORIAL:<br>
      Do something crazy<br>
      ]]></tutorial>
    <tracked_resources>
        <reset_on_restart_txt>Resets when the loop restarts.</reset_on_restart_txt>
        <!--countable items with names and counts on the top bar-->
        <resource no_reset_on_restart="true">
            <title>Mana:</title>
            <id>timer</id>
            <desc>Your main resource. The higher your mana, the more you can do before reset.</desc>
        </resource>
        <resource>
            <title>Gold:</title>
            <id>gold</id>
            <desc>Sell for mana, or use for actions.</desc>
        </resource>
        <resource initially_hidden="true">
            <title>Reputation:</title>
            <id>reputation</id>
            <desc>The influence you have over the people in town.</desc>
        </resource>
        <!--singular items with img icons rather than counts-->
        <!--<resource initially_hidden="true" no_count="true">
            <title><![CDATA[<img src="img/buyGlasses.svg" class="smallIcon">]]></title>
            <id>glasses</id>
            <desc>Woah, trees have so many leaves on them.</desc>
        </resource>-->
    </tracked_resources>
    <time_controls>
        <play_button>Play</play_button>
        <pause_button>Pause</pause_button>
        <pause_before_restart>Pause before restart</pause_before_restart>
        <pause_on_failed_loop>Pause on failed loop</pause_on_failed_loop>
        <restart_button>Restart</restart_button>
        <restart_text>Resets the loop. Not a hard reset.</restart_text>
        <hours>h</hours>
        <minutes>m</minutes>
        <seconds>s</seconds>
        <talents_button>Talents</talents_button>
        <story_title>Story</story_title>
        <stories>
            <story num="0">
                Wrong place and wrong time. You were visiting the city next to yours, looking for work, when monsters attacked! Wolves, trolls, ogres, even a chimera destroyed the town while you were hiding under cover.
                When your cover was destroyed by a stray fireball from the defenders, you ran out in the open - just in time for a platinum adventurer to conjure an elemental, accidentally right underneath you.
                You blacked out, and when you came to, the monsters were all defeated, and cleanup was underway. You helped for a bit, but then you suddenly collapsed - painlessly, thankfully - and the world went dark.
                You woke up, and you were back where you were, minutes ago! You were looping in time! Desperately, you tried to run, but in about the same time, it happened again.
                A few more loops, and you accidentally ran into a vase with water in it - and then the loop lasted just a little longer. After some experimentation, it seems that your mana is your clock, and when it runs out - time resets.
                Hopefully there's enough mana around you to get enough time to do something meaningful. For now, you need to search for more mana water, and figure out how to use it better.
            </story>
        </stories>
        <bonus_seconds>
            <title>Bonus Seconds</title>
            <main_text><![CDATA[
          When bonus is on, you get 4 extra seconds per second (5x faster).<br>
          Accrue 100% of paused or offline time as available bonus seconds. (capped at 1 month per offline period)<br>
          Bonus is
        ]]></main_text>
            <state>
                <on>ON</on>
                <off>OFF</off>
            </state>
            <counter_text>Total Bonus Seconds</counter_text>
        </bonus_seconds>
    </time_controls>
    <stats>
        <title>Stats</title>
        <con>
            <blurb>Turning thought into action. Your connection to your body.</blurb>
            <long_form>Control</long_form>
            <short_form>Con</short_form>
        </con>
        <per>
            <blurb>Your ability to gather information from the world around you. Your connection to your senses.</blurb>
            <long_form>Perception</long_form>
            <short_form>Per</short_form>
        </per>
        <ref>
            <blurb>Reaction time and muscle memory. Your connection to your instinct.</blurb>
            <long_form>Reflex</long_form>
            <short_form>Ref</short_form>
        </ref>
        <will>
            <blurb>Holding fast in the storm. Setting pain and discomfort aside for the sake of your goals. Your connection to your desire.</blurb>
            <long_form>Willpower</long_form>
            <short_form>Will</short_form>
        </will>
        <ele>
            <blurb>Holding yourself with dignity and grace: appearances matter. Your connection to your presense.</blurb>
            <long_form>Elegance</long_form>
            <short_form>Ele</short_form>
        </ele>
        <lead>
            <blurb>Understanding, directing, and inspiring. Your connection to your language.</blurb>
            <long_form>Leadership</long_form>
            <short_form>Lead</short_form>
        </lead>
        <soul>
            <blurb>You are the captain. Your connection to yourself.</blurb>
            <long_form>Soul</long_form>
            <short_form>Soul</short_form>
        </soul>
        <!--<dex>
            <blurb>Know your body.</blurb>
            <long_form>Dexterity</long_form>
            <short_form>Dex</short_form>
        </dex>-->

        <tooltip>
            <level>Level</level>
            <level_exp>Level Exp</level_exp>
            <exp>Exp</exp>
            <talent>Talent</talent>
            <talent_exp>Talent Exp</talent_exp>
            <talent_multiplier>Talent Mult</talent_multiplier>
            <soulstone>Soulstones</soulstone>
            <soulstone_multiplier>Soulstone Mult</soulstone_multiplier>
            <total_multiplier>Total Mult</total_multiplier>
            <bonus_xp>Bonus XP</bonus_xp>
            <explanation><![CDATA[
          Actions' mana costs are both how much mana they take, as well as time. Stats reduce the time/cost that each takes.
          Actions' mana costs are reduced by (stat levels)^.8 %<br>
          Every time you run the action, it gives stat exp equal its mana cost, spread across its given stat ratios.<br>
          The mana cost reduction from stats does not affect the amount of stat exp the action gives - only talent and soulstones affect the total exp an action gives.<br>
          1% of exp gained for the stat goes to talent. As talent levels up, it affects stat gain exp equal to Talent Mult.<br><br>
          Talent multiplies xp gain by (talentLevel / 50 + 1) ^ 0.4<br>
          Soulstones multiply xp gain by 1 + soulstones ^ .6 / 10<br>
          Total Mult is a combination of your talent and soulstone bonuses.<br><br>
          e.g. An action costs 800 mana and has a breakdown of <div class="bold">Con</div> 20% <div class="bold">Per</div> 80%.<br>
          This effectively means 160 of the mana is controlled by <div class="bold">Con</div>, and the remaining 640 by <div class="bold">Per</div>.<br>
          If your <div class="bold">Per</div> is level 20 when the action is started, the bonus would be (1.20)^.8=1.157 so it'd be 640 / 1.157 = 553.15<br>
          Adding back the 160 from <div class="bold">Con</div>, the total mana the action takes (rounded up) is now 713, so ~89% of the original mana cost.]]></explanation>
            <graph_legend><![CDATA[
          Click the legend to show/hide each.<br>
          Upon freshly starting, Levels and Talent won't change much.<br>
          Hover Stats for more info.]]></graph_legend>
        </tooltip>
        <view>
            <regular>Regular View</regular>
            <radar>Radar Chart</radar>
        </view>
    </stats>
    <skills>
        <title>Skills</title>
        <scombat>
            <label>Combat</label>
            <desc>Damage done</desc>
        </scombat>
        <manasense>
            <label>Mana Sense</label>
            <desc>To control mana, first you need to know how to feel it around you. Useful for finding where things are.</desc>
        </manasense>
        <manacontrol>
            <label>Mana Control</label>
            <desc>Control the mana to affect the world in mystical ways. Useful for both mana coming in or going out.</desc>
        </manacontrol>
        <weapons>
            <label>Weapons</label>
            <desc>Your ability to use weapons for fighting one on one, or long range.</desc>
        </weapons>
        <tooltip>
            <level>Level:</level>
            <level_exp>Level Exp:</level_exp>
            <no_reset_on_restart>Skills last through resets.</no_reset_on_restart>
        </tooltip>
    </skills>
    <buffs>
        <title>Buffs</title>
        <dark_ritual>
            <label>Dark Ritual</label>
            <desc>The witch appreciates your dedication to the dark arts. +1% to Dark Magic exp gain from the Dark Magic action (rounded down) per ritual.</desc>
            <desc2><![CDATA[<br>Actions are 10% faster in Beginnersville per ritual from 1-20.<br>
            Actions are 5% faster in the Forest Path per ritual from 21-40.<br>
            Actions are 2.5% faster in Merchanton per ritual from 41-60.<br>]]>
            </desc2>
        </dark_ritual>
        <tooltip>
            <level>Level</level>
            <no_reset_on_restart><![CDATA[Buffs last through resets.<br>You can click on the right hand number to edit it and adjust the cap for that buff. (buff actions will automatically fail and not spend soulstones past your set cap)]]></no_reset_on_restart>
        </tooltip>
    </buffs>
    <towns>
        <town0>
            <name>Startington</name>
            <desc>Recently shattered by a monster wave, it's got tons of things to fix.
            </desc>
        </town0>
        <town1>
            <name>Deep Well</name>
            <desc>You felt something big in here. It's time to find it.
            </desc>
        </town1>
    </towns>
    <actions>
        <title>Action Options</title>
        <title_stories>Action Stories</title_stories>
        <title_list>Action List</title_list>
        <active_title>Active</active_title>
        <next_title>Next</next_title>
        <title_loadout>Loadouts</title_loadout>
        <tooltip>
            <desc><![CDATA[
          Mana cost is based on ratio of stat %s.<br>
          Gained exp is proportional too.<br>
          Stat/Talent exp is gained every tick.<br>
          Skill exp is gained upon action completion unless otherwise specified.<br>
          Actions will target unchecked objects before known lootable objects.]]></desc>
            <mana_cost>Mana Cost</mana_cost>
            <exp_multiplier>Exp Multiplier</exp_multiplier>
            <mana_used>Mana Used</mana_used>
            <mana_used_explanation><![CDATA[
          Shows stat gain affecting speed.<br>
          Updates every completed action.<br>
          Accurate at end of run.]]></mana_used_explanation>
            <amount>Amount</amount>
            <current_list_active>Keep current list active</current_list_active>
            <repeat_last_action>Repeat last action on list</repeat_last_action>
            <add_action_top>Add action to top of list</add_action_top>
            <save_loadout>Save List</save_loadout>
            <load_loadout>Load Selected List</load_loadout>
            <clear_list>Clear List</clear_list>
            <higher_done_percent_benefic>You can find more stuff with higher %.</higher_done_percent_benefic>
            <progress_label>Progress</progress_label>
            <total_found>Total Found</total_found>
            <total_checked>Total Checked</total_checked>
            <icons>
                <circle>Cap to current max</circle>
                <plus>Add one loop</plus>
                <minus>Subtract one loop</minus>
                <arrows_h>Split action</arrows_h>
                <sort_up>Move action up</sort_up>
                <sort_down>Move action down</sort_down>
                <circles>Enable/disable action</circles>
                <times>Remove action</times>
            </icons>
            <list_explanation><![CDATA[
      Drag and drop the actions to re-arrange them.<br>
      The next list becomes the current list every restart.<br>
      One second = 100 mana.<br>
      Minimum 1 tick per action.<br>
      Restarts automatically upon no actions left.]]></list_explanation>
        </tooltip>
        <current_action>
            <mana_original>Mana Original:</mana_original>
            <mana_used>Mana Used:</mana_used>
            <mana_remaining>Mana Remaining:</mana_remaining>
            <gold_remaining>Gold Remaining:</gold_remaining>
            <time_spent>Time Spent:</time_spent>
            <failed_attempts>Failed Attempts:</failed_attempts>
            <error>Error:</error>
        </current_action>
        <!--town 1-->
        <sense_potions>
            <label>Sense Potions</label>
            <label_done>Mana Potions Sensed</label_done>
            <tooltip>You need mana immediately, to keep going. You're not proud of this, but you'll be searching through mana potions that the town's defenders... left behind.
                Straining your ability to sense mana starts to pay off... permanently. Becomes 100% more effective for each mana sense level.</tooltip>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>50% Checked:</b>⮀ You've found all of the easy potions. You can tell there are some under rubble, but your Mana Sense skill has to be a bit higher to find them.]]></story_1>
            <story_2><![CDATA[<b>100% Checked:</b>⮀ You've checked everywhere, and all of the available potions in town are known to you.]]></story_2>
        </sense_potions>
        <drink_potion>
            <label>Drink Potion</label>
            <label_done>Potions Drunk</label_done>
            <info_text1>Pots with mana left</info_text1>
            <info_text2>Pots with mana total</info_text2>
            <info_text3>Pots to check for mana</info_text3>
            <tooltip><![CDATA[
            Some of them have mana left, sometimes the mana sense is pinging off of a different potion. No choice but to drink it to figure it out. Each good potion gives
        ]]></tooltip>
            <tooltip2><![CDATA[
              mana. Every 2 potions are good. You can choose to drink the good ones first with "lootable first" checked.
        ]]></tooltip2>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>10 Pots with mana:</b>⮀ ]]></story_1>
        </drink_potion>
        <dive_into_well>
            <label>Dive Into Well</label>
            <tooltip><![CDATA[
            While searching for mana potions, you felt something much bigger, although further away. After searching all around town, you've found the strongest source - down the well.
            You don't have much time, so you dive in to figure out what's down there.
            <br>Unlocked when Mana Sense is at least 2.
        ]]></tooltip>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>Dove in:</b>⮀ The water is cold, and you have to find a way out. After swimming for a bit, you find an access point and start to swim up, reaching a cave dimly lit by glowing crystals. Crystals that have mana in them. You know what to do next.]]></story_1>
        </dive_into_well>
        <get_well_mana>
            <label>Get Well Mana</label>
            <tooltip>Now you know where the mana source is, so you can go right to it and absorb it. There's a problem, however - you'll need a ladder to go back to the source from that direction.
                Cost reduces by 50 for each Mana Control level past 10, down to a cost of 1000. Gives 4000 mana. You of course can't both do this and go into the well to get it again.</tooltip>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>Source Absorbed:</b>⮀ Using the ladder, you easily go to the mana source in the well and absorb it.]]></story_1>
        </get_well_mana>
        <buy_ladder>
            <label>Buy Ladder</label>
            <tooltip>Ladder time</tooltip>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>Ladder Purchased:</b>⮀ Climb]]></story_1>
        </buy_ladder>
        <gain_mana>
            <label>Gain Mana</label>
            <tooltip>TEST</tooltip>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>TESTTT:</b>⮀ Climb]]></story_1>
        </gain_mana>
        <learn_healing>
            <label>Learn Healing</label>
            <label_done>Learned from Healing Book</label_done>
            <tooltip>HEAL</tooltip>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>50% Checked:</b>⮀ ]]></story_1>
            <story_2><![CDATA[<b>100% Checked:</b>⮀ ]]></story_2>
        </learn_healing>

        <!-- well -->
        <sense_crystals>
            <label>Sense Crystals</label>
            <label_done>Mana Crystals Sensed</label_done>
            <tooltip>You can feel mana crystals around you. They're in rubble and dirt piles, shaken loose from the battles that were fought above. Becomes 100% more effective for each mana sense level.</tooltip>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>50% Checked:</b>⮀ You've found most of the mana crystals.]]></story_1>
            <story_2><![CDATA[<b>100% Checked:</b>⮀ You've checked everywhere, and all of the available crystals in the well are known to you.]]></story_2>
        </sense_crystals>
        <uncover_crystal>
            <label>Uncover Crystal</label>
            <label_done>Crystals Uncovered</label_done>
            <info_text1>Crystals with mana left</info_text1>
            <info_text2>Crystals with mana total</info_text2>
            <info_text3>Crystals to check for mana</info_text3>
            <tooltip><![CDATA[
            Luckily, there is an shovel nearby. You work to remove the covering dirt, and reveal crystals with fresh mana in them. Each good crystal gives
        ]]></tooltip>
            <tooltip2><![CDATA[
             mana. Every Mana Control level increases mana a crystal gives by 10, until it gives 800. Every 2 crystals are good. You can choose to drink the good ones first with "lootable first" checked.
        ]]></tooltip2>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>5 Crystals with mana:</b>⮀ You're steadily improving the mana you can get from these crystals, but you've taken from all that have mana.]]></story_1>
            <story_2><![CDATA[<b>Mana Control 20:</b>⮀ Every bit of mana from the crystals is pulled out when you try.]]></story_2>
        </uncover_crystal>
        <explore_tunnels>
            <label>Explore Tunnels</label>
            <label_done>Tunnels Explored</label_done>
            <tooltip>There's lots of branching paths. Time to look through all of them! You'll find more mana crystals on the way. This action is required to move on. Unlocks at 100% Mana Crystals Sensed. Becomes 100% more effective for each mana sense level.</tooltip>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>50% Checked:</b>⮀ You've run into a lot of dead ends and collapsed tunnels. The further you get, the older this place seems - and the more dangerous.]]></story_1>
            <story_2><![CDATA[<b>80% Checked:</b>⮀ There's been a few grooves in the walls or floors you've seen - traps are ahead. So far, all of them have been triggered already.]]></story_2>
            <story_3><![CDATA[<b>100% Checked:</b>⮀ This is as far as you can go before you can see active traps in front of you. You've explored everywhere without them. From now on, you only need a short jaunt through the tunnels to collect the mana, and you'll reach these traps.]]></story_3>
        </explore_tunnels>
        <discover_traps>
            <label>Discover Traps</label>
            <label_done>Traps Found</label_done>
            <tooltip>Look for traps in the tunnels before you move on. Figure out how to avoid them or disarm them. Requires Explore Tunnels before you can run this action. Unlocks at 100% Explore Tunnels. Becomes 100% more effective for each mana sense level.</tooltip>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>100% Checked:</b>⮀ After nearly being killed many times, there's only one trap room that matters, and beyond it you can see more branching paths, as well as feel a stronger presence of mana. If you can just get rid of these traps... Maybe these switches will help?]]></story_1>
        </discover_traps>
        <switch1>
            <label>Switch 1</label>
            <tooltip>While searching around for traps, you find a switch in the wall. You flip it, but nothing seems to happen. Maybe there are other switches to find.</tooltip>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>Switch flipped:</b>⮀ Nothing obvious happens - maybe you need more switches?]]></story_1>
        </switch1>
        <switch2>
            <label>Switch 2</label>
            <tooltip>Another switch, in the floor this time. Switching it, or both the first and this one, result in nothing happening. You keep searching</tooltip>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>Switch flipped:</b>⮀ Nothing obvious happens - maybe you need more switches?]]></story_1>
        </switch2>
        <switch3>
            <label>Switch 3</label>
            <tooltip>A third switch, disguised as a candle holder! Flipping all 3 switches, you can hear a clink in the walls - Maybe you can get in and remove the trap mechanism now.</tooltip>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>Switch flipped:</b>⮀ Nothing obvious happens - maybe you need more switches?]]></story_1>
        </switch3>
        <disarm_traps>
            <label>Disarm Traps</label>
            <tooltip>With all the switches flipped, you can disable the whole mechanism.</tooltip>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>Traps Disarmed:</b>⮀ Pulling a final lever, you hear a clink, a shutter, and something grinds to a halt. You're reasonably certain it's finally safe to continue.]]></story_1>
        </disarm_traps>
        <explore_deep>
            <label>Explore Deep</label>
            <label_done>Deep Tunnels Explored</label_done>
            <tooltip>Past the traps, you find an even older area, more cavelike than the construction of before. There are mana veins here, filled with uesful mana. Still, they don't feel like the last piece you've been sensing all along. Becomes 100% more effective for each mana sense level.</tooltip>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>50% Checked:</b>⮀ ]]></story_1>
            <story_2><![CDATA[<b>100% Checked:</b>⮀ ]]></story_2>
        </explore_deep>
        <absorb_vein>
            <label>Absorb Vein</label>
            <label_done>Veins Absorbed</label_done>
            <info_text1>Veins with mana left</info_text1>
            <info_text2>Veins with mana total</info_text2>
            <info_text3>Veins to check for mana</info_text3>
            <tooltip><![CDATA[
            Requires you to disarm the traps to get to these veins. Each vein gives
        ]]></tooltip>
            <tooltip2><![CDATA[
              mana. Every Mana Control level past 10 increases mana a vein gives by 25, until it gives 2000. Every vein is full of mana.
        ]]></tooltip2>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>5 veins with mana:</b>⮀ The veins thankfully keep you going, and give you the time needed for the trial ahead.]]></story_1>
        </absorb_vein>
        <get_to_source>
            <label>Get To Source</label>
            <tooltip>You've explored the area, and only one path remains - the one to the source. It's long, but the reward will be worth it.</tooltip>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>Traveled to Source:</b>⮀ It's beautiful.]]></story_1>
        </get_to_source>
        <absorb_source>
            <label>Absorb Source</label>
            <tooltip>The motherlode. The mana is deep and still, yet blinding in its quantity. It will take a lot of control to get it out. Cost reduces by 50 for each Mana Control level past 10, down to a cost of 800. Gives 4000 mana.</tooltip>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>Source Absorbed:</b>⮀ After a mighty struggle, the power fills you. Finally, you have time to do more now. First, however, is figuring out how to get out quickly.]]></story_1>
        </absorb_source>
        <escape_routes>
            <label>Escape Routes</label>
            <label_done>Escape Routes Checked</label_done>
            <tooltip>With the light of the motherlode fading, you can see more tunnels ahead. Some are leading up - maybe you'll find a way out? Requires Absorb Source to be completed.</tooltip>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>100% Checked:</b>⮀ You found it - a way out. You nearly cry in relief. Unfortunately, it's pretty high up.]]></story_1>
        </escape_routes>
        <escape_well>
            <label>Escape Well</label>
            <tooltip>It's finally time to leave this well. The way out was down a cliff before you finally saw a small light in the ceiling, and after piling up some rocks to get to handholds, you're out. Run this action once to unlock new ones.</tooltip>
            <story_1><![CDATA[<b>Escaped:</b>⮀ You climb and shimmy out, and then there's a wood floor above you, partially cracked.
            You open it a little more and find a house in ruins, but with the quantity of bottles around, you can see it as the alchemist's shop, or at least it was.
            Now that you know where you are, you could get back down much easier. That is, if you had the time to both do that and absorb the motherlode.
            You spot a bookshelf with most of the books destroyed, but an Introduction to Magical Healing book is intact.]]></story_1>
        </escape_well>



    </actions>
    <spells>
        <title>Spells</title>
    </spells>
</body>
