<?xml version="1.0"?>
<body>
  <menu>
    <changelog>
      <meta>
        <title>Changelog</title>
        <version_prefix>Version</version_prefix>
      </meta>
      <version verNum=".73"><![CDATA[
          * Changed formula for how Old Shortcut reduces Continue On<br>
          * Repeat last action on list saves now<br>
          * Lootable first checkboxes save now<br>
          * Window title switches when paused correctly<br>
          * Dragging an action image doesn't change the URL in firefox<br>
          * 2 more story parts, unlocked at Small Dungeon completion<br>
          * Re-arrange icon/loop count order on lists<br>
          * Get Drunk removes 2 gold instead of adding it
        ]]></version>
        <version verNum=".72"><![CDATA[
            * Sound on pause available in options<br>
            * training limit set to 50 from 10 (for now)<br>
            * Mana Original is multipled by # loops<br>
            * Travel Action styling change<br>
            * Saving in town 3<br>
            * DRAG AND DROP (Thanks to Hunter)
      ]]></version>
        <version verNum=".71"><![CDATA[
            * Tooltip on reset button<br>
            * Glasses give x2 to forest<br>
            * Mana cost reflects the tooltips now rather than an average of stat reduction<br>
            * Trainings are capped at 10 per loop<br>
            * New actions! Brew Potions, Continue On, Explore City, Gamble, Get Drunk, Purchase Mana, Sell Potions<br>
            * Some new actions are usless at the moment.
      ]]></version>
        <version verNum=".70"><![CDATA[
            * Reverted skill nerf (too harsh)<br>
            * Actually capped glasses<br>
            * Sell Gold -> Buy Mana<br>
            * Double soulstone recovery<br>
            * Nerfed practical magic (more uses for it later)
      ]]></version>
        <version verNum=".69"><![CDATA[
            * Nerfed the soulstone nerf<br>
            * Cleared additional purple bars on exp<br>
            * Corrected glasses/throw party tooltips<br>
            * Actually nerfed skill growth - it's cheaper than before for level 2 - 23, and about 4x harder at level 100<br>
            * Add action to top of list option
      ]]></version>
        <version verNum=".68"><![CDATA[
            * Added tab icon<br>
            * Throw Party costs 2 reputation from 3<br>
            * Removed Guided Tour<br>
            * Added Buy Glasses<br>
            * Fixed later segment names for Fight<br>
            * Nerfed soulstones<br>
            * Changed soulstone gathering, equalling about half previous rate but more initially<br>
            * Nerfed skill growth<br>
            * Added Options and Discord Link (to be expanded)<br>
            * Start Journey cost 2k -> 1k
      ]]></version>
        <version verNum=".67"><![CDATA[
            * Added FAQ<br>
            * Doubled effectiveness of Guided Tour<br>
            * Fixed majority of memory leaks (not all)<br>
            * Made Heal/Fight requirements visible with training unlock<br>
            * Lengthened action list div<br>
            * Changed some wording of descriptions for clarity<br>
            * Added "lootable first" option, credit to Hunter<br>
            * Fixed a bug with extreme gain on Heal
      ]]></version>
        <version verNum=".66"><![CDATA[
            * Mostly fixed import being all weird<br>
            * Changed investigate to be visible earlier<br>
            * Fixed Old Shortcut to be 100% from 110%<br>
            * Fixed Investigate to be 100% from 90%<br>
            * Rewording old shortcut and hermit<br>
            * Game autopauses if current list is empty<br>
            * Saves variables even if they're 0 (fixes some incorrect negative values)<br>
            * Fixes your save if your variables were negative.
      ]]></version>
        <version verNum=".65"><![CDATA[
            * Added Learn Alchemy action and Alchemy skill<br>
            * Made a reddit post and discord<br>
            * Hid Skills that are at 0 exp<br>
            * Import/export
      ]]></version>
        <version verNum=".64"><![CDATA[
            * Start Journey costs 2k mana from 1k<br>
            * Added Old Shortcut, Talk to Hermit, and Practical Magic actions<br>
            * Added Practical Magic skill<br>
            * Widened version tooltips
      ]]></version>
        <version verNum=".63"><![CDATA[
            * Made Heal the Sick, Fight Monster, and Clear Dungeon more difficult<br>
            * Changing forEach to for loops, I forgot to change return to continue, causing multiple large issues<br>
            * Made stat window a little larger<br>
            * Changed town numbers to update on reload, instead of just on a new %
      ]]></version>
        <version verNum=".62"><![CDATA[
            * Added Gather Wild Mana, Gather Herbs, Hunt, and Sit Under Waterfall<br>
            * Hide supplies/herbs/hide if you have 0<br>
            * You'll need to complete 1 more % on Forest Explored to update Mana Sources (NOTE: not anymore)<br>
      ]]></version>
        <version verNum=".61"><![CDATA[
            * Removed beautiful forEach loops because IE can't handle them<br>
            * Possibly fixes game not working on iPads too (tell me if so)<br>
            * Fixed errors for players with no save file<br>
            * Adjusted mana costs for new actions
      ]]></version>
        <version verNum=".6"><![CDATA[
            * Added version info<br>
            * Added Haggle, Buy Supplies, Start Journey, Explore Forest<br>
            * Added switching towns and town names<br>
            * Added error messages when an action fails (red bar)<br>
            * Require reputation now requires, instead of costs<br>
            * Fixed repeating a last action with a cost bug<br>
            * Visually separated resources and main actions<br>
            * Reduced requirements/difficulty for heal/fight/dungeon<br>
            * WARNING: adblock caused game to freeze. This has no ads, disable if you also freeze<br>
            * Improved performance (since I was looking anyway)
      ]]></version>
    </changelog>
    <save>
      <meta>
        <title>Saving</title>
      </meta>
      <manual_save>Save Manually</manual_save>
      <input_label>Export/Import</input_label>
      <export_button>Export</export_button>
      <export_comment><![CDATA[Click Export to export to your clipboard (ctrl-v somewhere else).<br>
              Paste a save and click Import to import.]]></export_comment>
              <import_button>Import</import_button>
              <import_comment><![CDATA[
              WARNING: Import will break the game if invalid save. Empty import will hard clear the game<br>
              If you reaaallly want to edit your save file, <div class="showthat2">hover me<div class="showthis2">In the console, use decode("pasted savefile"), edit, then encode('pasted savefile'), then import it<br>This is mainly for fixing broken savefiles - don't be a cheater.</div></div>]]></import_comment>
    </save>
    <faq>
      <meta>
        <title>FAQ</title>
        <q_prefix>Q</q_prefix>
        <a_prefix>Q</a_prefix>
      </meta>
        <q_a>
          <q>What do stats do?</q>
          <a>Hover over "Stats" for how they work. What stats are important depend on what actions you need that uses them.</a>
        </q_a>
        <q_a>
          <q>Short runs seem better.</q>
          <a> Short runs are better, for the early game and current balance. As your runs get longer and you accrue talent and soulstones they become more useful.</a>
        </q_a>
        <q_a>
          <q>What should my first goal be?</q>
          <a>Start with wandering until you have ways of getting mana back. Then try to find how to get some combat training which gives you a permanent boost, and then try fighting monsters!</a>
        </q_a>
      </faq>
    <options>
      <meta>
        <title>Options</title>
      </meta>
      <discord>
        <link>https://discord.gg/EmRuWPp</link>
        <title>Discord Link</title>
      </discord>
      <adblock_warning>WARNING: for some reason Adblock Plus can cause massive lag. I won't ever have ads so if your game is freezing frequently please disable for this page.</adblock_warning>
      <pause_audio_cue>Ping on pause</pause_audio_cue>
    </options>
  </menu>
</body>
